NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
Huh, it's Tsunade-sama.
Huh? You guys are...
Hey, are you visiting someone
at the hospital too?
Yes.
You too, Tsunade-sama?
Well I guess...
She just doesn't want to stay
in the executive office...
Shut up!
Hinata, don't faint when
you see Kurenai-sensei.
P-Please let's not talk about that.
Did something happen?
When we were visiting Naruto
in the hospital in the past...
Shino!
This girl fainted when she saw Naruto
all covered with bandages.
Kiba!
I'll... I'll be fine this time!
I finally found you...!
Grandma Tsunade, I need
to talk to you!
Huh? Hinata!
Naruto...
— Naruto is... so close!
— Hinata? Hinata! What's wrong?
Your face looks a little red...
Do you have a fever or something? Huh?
Hey...
H-Hey, Hinata...?!
Hey, Hinata!
Are you okay?!
Get a hold of yourself!
Hinata!
Naruto...
Akamaru Gets Jealous of the
Super Following Ability!
Find the Illusionary
Scent Bug
Hey, you woke up.
So Mizuki didn't know anything
you said?
Tsunade interrogated him herself.
He didn't have any information
that would lead to Orochimaru's
current whereabouts...
After all that guy was nothing but
a disposable pawn to Orochimaru, huh.
So it seems...
We still don't know where
Sasuke went...
And that's the result after
a desperate fight with Mizuki...
That can't sit right with
Naruto either... huh?
Please Grandma Tsunade
say it's okay!
When I say no I mean no!
As a result Tsunade-sama wasn't able
to concentrate on her work.
Naruto's been breathing down
her neck the whole time
asking her to let him go off
in search of Sasuke.
So she sneaked out
of her office but...
He was lying in wait for her here.
Naruto...
I've asked you numerous times already!
Please let me go in search
of Sasuke!
I've told you numerous times already.
Impossible!
Why!
You have some training to do!
I can't because Pervy Sage
isn't around!
We have zero leads on either
Orochimaru and Sasuke.
So how are you planning
to search for him?
I can figure it out somehow!
If there aren't any leads
I'll go find some!
So please let me go do it!
You're stubborn aren't you?
You're stubborn too,
Grandma Tsunade!
— Please let me go!
— No, you may not!
If I say I'm going, I'm going!
Shut up! No means no!
Byakugan!
All right! Good work, Neji!
Move in another half step
right there!
Yes sir!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's take a break, Neji.
Yes.
Have some tea too.
Thank you...
If Hinata was here
she should have observed a little.
Hinata prepared this...?
It would supplement her training
by observing...
Byakugan!
Let's take a break.
— Yes.
— Food! Food!
That was pretty well done.
I would say that you're getting closer
to perfecting the technique.
It's thanks to you both.
You're so kind to join me
in my special training every day...
We're a team.
When a comrade in the team
is in a fix
one offers a helping hand.
That's only natural...
A comrade...
If a comrade suddenly disappears
it must be awfully hard.
You're talking about Naruto,
aren't you?
Isn't there some way
we could help him?
I'd like to help him out in
some way too... but...
Hokage-sama was telling Naruto...
that there are no leads at all.
There may be one resource...
Really?!
I'm talking about Bikochu.
Bikochu?
Are you talking about
those rare insects...?!
I have heard that they had
become extinct some time ago.
Since there was a possibility
that they could become extinct
the Aburame Clan discontinued
using them
so a minuscule number of them
should still be alive.
Tsunade-sama, what are Bikochu?
Well... it's not surprising that
you don't know about them.
The last time that Bikochu
were used
was before the last Great War...
Bikochu are one kind of insect
used by insect handlers.
Larvae which have hatched from eggs
become chrysalises in no time at all
then emerge and turn
into imagos.
They are then made to
recognize scents...
and they are able to track
even the faintest scent...
to its source.
Their olfactory sense is several thousand
times greater than a Ninja Hound's.
They are insects capable of
exhibiting that skill in an exceptional way.
However, Bikochu lay eggs
only once every several years...
This year is actually the year
in which they lay eggs.
And right now is exactly
the time when they hatch.
I see.
There are still some of
Sasuke's belongings left in the village...
Right?
If one makes the Bikochu
recognize that scent...
We may be able to locate
Sasuke's whereabouts, right?
What is the probability
of finding a Bikochu?
Frankly speaking not very high.
Perhaps 10%.
10%, huh...
As you guys know
the situation in the village
is currently very grave...
We don't have the leeway of allowing
even Genin to sit around and play.
However fortunately or unfortunately
Kurenai has been hospitalized
so you guys Team 8
no longer have a mission.
Rather than just letting
you sit around and play
I'd rather place my bet
on that 10% possibility.
Huh... you mean...
Aburame Shino. Inuzuka Kiba.
Hyuga Hinata.
I order you to search for
the Bikochu!
— All right!
I designate Shino
as the leader this time.
And... that spy up there!
Oww...!
Naruto...
You're going to go even if
I try to stop you right?
Yup!
In that case I have no choice
but to let you go...
However...
This is your last chance.
If you don't find the Bikochu...
you must give up on Sasuke!
— Wha...?
— You understand?!
It'll be fine...
I'll find it without fail.
All right. You won't go back
on your word right?
Yeah! Leave it to me!
You're easily pleased, aren't you?
Owww!
Naruto...
Sasuke...
Hinata.
Good morning.
Neji will be here soon
for his training...
Please prepare tea as always.
Well...
Huh? What's the matter?
I need to go...
on a mission starting now...
A mission, huh...
In that case it can't be helped...
I'm heading out...
Don't be a burden to the others.
Yes sir!
I'm... I'm sorry! I'm in a hurry...
The way she handled
her physical response just now...
Hinata...
You're late, Hinata!
I'm sorry!
All right then! Let's head out!
Let's go!
Huh?
Why are you walking at
such a leisurely pace?!
It takes a Shinobi two days on foot
to get to the habitat of
the Bikochu...
There's no need to make haste
from the very start.
But what if the eggs hatch
before we get there?
The eggs of Bikochu only hatch
on the day after it's rained...
There's no sign of it
raining any time soon...
But... if by some remote chance...
Naruto.
Wh-What is it?
I am the leader of this team.
While we are on this mission
you will obey the orders of your leader.
Kiba, I can't believe you're able
to work with that kind of guy...
Well I've gotten used to it...
I'm sure you'll bond with him too, Naruto.
I wonder about that...
Naruto and the others
left a while ago.
I see.
Didn't you want to go too?
When it comes to searching
for insects
Shino who's an insect handler
is number one...
And then Hinata who has Byakugan...
and Kiba and Akamaru who have
sensitive noses are there too...
So there's really no role that
I could play!
What I must do right now...
is to become a Medical Ninja
as soon as I possibly can!
What's the matter, Shino?!
The sun's going down.
We're setting up camp.
Got it.
— Huh?
— Okay.
Huh? What...?!
We're gonna set up
camp already?!
I'm not tired at all yet!
Let's go further!
Naruto, the leader of
this team is me.
I-I understand!
Okay then... let's sleep.
Huh... we're gonna sleep already?!
Many animals and plants
go to sleep at sunset
and awake at sunrise.
In order to search for insects
we must understand the rhythm
of living creatures with our own bodies...
But... the sun's just set...
Naruto, I am the leader of this team...
Okay, okay. I got it!
There's no way
I can sleep so early...
Yeah right...
All that complaining and guess
who's the first one to fall asleep?
I have to pee...
Huh?
What's that?
It's a waterfall...
Hey... Is somebody there?
S-Say...
Damn it...!
S-Sorry. Did I scare you?
Huh?
There's nobody there...
Huh, Naruto...
Did you catch a cold?
Yeah... a little...
After sleeping so much
you're still tired?
Well uh...
When I woke up last night to pee
I saw something awesome...
Did you catch a cold too, Hinata?
No, I'm okay...
And... what was that awesome thing?
It was a beautiful woman
in the middle of the waterfall!
Huh?
When that person moved her arms
the water would suddenly move too!
It was awesome!
And what happened then...
When I tried to speak to her
she suddenly vanished.
You must have been dreaming
or something.
It's starting to feel that way...
You idiot!
Your face is red, Hinata.
You might have really
caught a cold.
Huh... really I'm fine...
This fruit is edible.
This will be our meal today.
Got it.
We can save on
our food supplies too.
There's one thing
I need to warn you about.
On rare occasions this fruit grows
to the size of a human being.
However those fruits
are damaged inside.
Don't tamper with them
under any circumstance.
There's nobody who would
eat something that huge.
N-Naruto...!
He's eating it...
Naruto... We're going on ahead...
I'll... I'll be right behind you!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wait just a second!
Hey... aren't we there yet?
Yes.
We're here!
What...?
Wow!
I've never seen anything
like this before.
This certainly isn't a place
where humans could inhabit.
That's right...
That's why it's paradise for insects.
D-Don't tell me...
Could it be that... over there...?
You mean that's where
the Bikochu are?
No problem.
It's better than the Chunin Exam.
Damn... The foothold crumbles easily...
— Naruto...
— What?
As the leader I'm warning you...
At a time like this
what is it?!
Don't fall.
I already know that
without your telling me!
Naruto!
No way...!
That was close...
Those were insects, huh...
That's why I warned you.
When this mission is over
I'm definitely gonna kick
that guy's butt!
This is... the Bikochu forest.
Let's go.
There's no mistake.
Those are Leaf Shinobi.
The fact that those guys came to
a place like this
means their objective is...
Yeah... it's the same as ours...
the Bikochu.
We're not gonna let them
take any Bikochu.
The Bikochu...
belong to us the Kamizuru Clan!
kusottare na nyuusu ga toori sugite
crappy news pass us by
kimi wa kotoba wo nakusu
and you become speechless
boku no koe ja marude chiisa sugite
my voice is way too soft
kimi wa henji mo shinai
so you don't answer
kimi ga naiteru hitori de naiteru
you're crying, crying alone
boku wa dou suru boku mo naiteru no sa
what can I do? I'm crying too
yoru ni hitoribocchi no ore no sakebi ni nosete
"let my lonely scream ring out through the night"
zawameku jidai wo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash this confused era with my speed, yeah
sanzameku yoru mo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
and I'll thrash this confused night with my speed, yeah
tsunzaku gitaa to ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar and my speed, yeah
katamuku sekai mo warui yatsura mo kechirashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll take this sinking world, all its evil bastards, and kick their butts, yeah
Huh! If you're talking about
the insect in this photograph
I'm very familiar with it.
— Huh?
— Really?!
Damn... Don't tell me
that was a Bikochu?
Where did you see it?
I heard some rustling in the kitchen
in the middle of the night
and I unintentionally threw
a slipper at it...
Wait a second...
N-Naruto...
What you're talking about
is an ordinary cockroach.
Next time:
"How is it Different?! All Bugs Look the Same, Don't They??"